An Ordinary Man is a action, drama, war film directed by Brad Silberling.
A war criminal in hiding forms a relationship with his only
connection to the outside world - his maid.
The General, played by Ben Kingsley.
Tanja, played by Hera Hilmar.
Miro, played by Peter Serafinowicz.
ER Intern, played by Edmund Kingsley.
Grocer, played by Robert Blythe.
Policeman, played by Milorad Kapor.
An Ordinary Man is a 2017 American drama thriller film
written, directed and produced by Brad Silberling.
It stars Ben Kingsley, Hera Hilmar and Peter Serafinowicz.
Filmed in Belgrade, Serbia in 2015, it was screened at the Bari International Film Festival in April 2017
and picked up in February 2018 by Saban Films, who released it direct-to-video in June 2018.
The tone is emotional.